{
    "id": "01ceda0cd95841ab9d25dba764a0491b",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You will not succeed …………………. you work hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. the train was late, I managed to reach on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited ………………….. the train arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "unless",
                "till"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you are called, you must come in at once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot give you any money, ……………. I have none.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He fled ………………. he should be killed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t go ………………. he hadn’t invited me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked …………….. he could take a day off work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "as if",
                "weather"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She smiled ……………… she knew everything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as",
                "even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you are mistaken, or I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}